"Hi, we are Mark & Angie Gray and 'MGBD Parts' is the part of our business dedicated to keeping Rover P6 cars on the road at cost"
effective prices.
"We have over 30 years experience of owning, repairing, restoring and running Rover P6 cars in all variants, 2000, 2200 & 3500, saloon and estate, both as everyday and show cond ition cars. Our current fleet includes an everyday user  1966 Rover 2000, and also a 1972 Rover 2000TC export,  1975 Rover 2200 Auto,  1972 Rover 3500 Estoura (estate)  and of course, the last P6 off the production  line 'WC 700S',  the avocado Rover 3500S. We have had over 25 years involvement in classic car clubs mostly at committee level and have now turned our specialist knowledge and experience into our Rover P6 parts business  'MGBD Parts', which is dedicated to supplying quality parts for all variants of the Rover P6 built between  1963-1977. The parts stocked are predominantly brand new manufactured items but there is also a mix of  'NOS' (New Old Stock), refurbished service exchange and second hand parts. But if you can't see what you need please email or call us. Also if you need any advice or technical help, we are only a phone call away and we'll be glad to help and what's more, that's free!."
"Please note that all Refurbished, NOS and Secondhand parts are detailed as such in the webstore, and therefore anything else listed is"
"a brand new manufactured item. You can click on the categories list on the left of the webstore or use the product search facility to look through our items by description or by part number. To make life easier for you we have listed all of the parts by the original Rover parts numbers that were used in the Rover Parts catalogues, so you can look your part up by its Rover part number. If you don't fmd what you are looking for, again please call or drop us an email"
"The shop also has a facility for you to register as a 'user' and by doing this, we can save your contact details for future purchases and"
"then you'll only have to log in, which saves you time when you are purchasing parts. You can also save your 'Shopping Basket' and return at a later date if you need to. Registered users will be emailed period ically with details of our latest parts, offers and other news via the shop's newsletter which will start shortly, however please check out our 'Important Customer Information' and 'Privacy' pages for the legal stuff The webstore has been live since July 2012 and has new items being added daily and is therefore growing everyday, so you really do need to refresh your browser every time you visit us. We have set up a competitive set of shipping rates and offer combined shipping rates for multiple purchases but please ask if a shipping rate doesn't seem right for you."
"Also,  we attend many shows and events throughout the UK during the year and if you want to save costs on shipping, you can"
arrange to meet us at these events and collect your parts from us in person. Details of the events we will be attend ing will be on the diary page along with the dates of the monthly Wolverhampton RSR All Rover Meet.
"So please call, text or email if you don't see what you need or if you just need technical advice."
email sales@rngbdparts.co.uk    Phone land line +44 (0)1902 689975
